export const Quiz = [
  {
    question: "Wich was the first calculator?",
    options: ["Perfored sheets", "Abacus", "Microsoft calculator", "The human fingers"],
    answer: "Abacus"
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the Apple creator?",
    options: ["Steve Jobs", "Linus Torvalds", "Bill Gates", "Jeff Bezos"],
    answer: "Steve Jobs"
  },
  {
    question: "How was called the Pascal machine?",
    options: ["Abacus", "Pascal Machine", "Typewriter", "Pascaline"],
    answer: "Pascaline"
  },
  {
    question: "How many computers generations are there?",
    options: ["1", "The computers has generations?", "7", "4"],
    answer: "7"
  },
  {
    question: "What material were the first computers made of?",
    options: ["Transistors", "Empty pipes", "Microchips", "All of above"],
    answer: "Empty pipes"
  },
  {
    question: "What are the current OS?",
    options: ["Mac OS, Windows, Linux", "Mac OS, Windows 10, Ubuntu", "Windows 10, Windows 11, Fedora 35", "Mac OS and Windows"],
    answer: "Mac OS, Windows, Linux"
  },
  {
    question: "How much did the first computer weigh?",
    options: ["A lot", "100 Kg", "Like a Mammoth", "27 Tons"],
    answer: "27 Tons"
  },
  {
    question: "Wich was the first microprocessor and by whom was created?",
    options: ["PIC-18F4620, Intel", "Threadripper, AMD", "4004, Intel", "8008, Intel"],
    answer: "4004, Intel"
  },
  {
    question: "When Setve Jobs died?",
    options: ["November 5, 2011", "October 15, 2011", "Ten years ago", "October 5, 2011"],
    answer: "October 5, 2011"
  },
  {
    question: "When was created the first computer?",
    options: ["1971", "1930", "1956", "1969"],
    answer: "1971"
  }
]